The light runs out
The Tunnel is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Carlo Ledesma.
In 2007, in the midst of the drought and water shortages, the NSW State government has unveiled plans to tap into and recycle
millions of litres of water trapped in a network of abandoned train tunnels just beneath the heart of Sydney.
However the government suddenly goes cold on the
plan and it is not made public why.
There is talk of homeless people who use the tunnel as shelter going missing, even
though the government states that there are no homeless people in there.
This, and the silence from the officials and ministers, leads a journalist,
Natasha to begin an investigation into a government cover-up.
She and her crew Pete (Producer), Steve (Cameraman) and Tangles (Sound
Technichian) decide to investigate the story in the tunnel.
Natasha Warner, played by Bel Deliá.
Jim 'Tangles' Williams, played by Luke Arnold.
Peter Ferguson, played by Andy Rodoreda.
Trevor Jones, played by James Caitlin.
Stalker, played by Goran D. Kleut.
Kate, played by Arianna Gusi.
The Tunnel is a 2011 Australian found-footage monster horror film directed by Carlo Ledesma (in his feature-length
directorial debut) and co-written, co-produced, and co-edited by Julian Harvey and Enzo Tedeschi.
The film stars Bel Deliá, Andy Rodoreda, Steve Davis, Luke Arnold, Goran D.
Kleut, and James Caitlin in a documentary-style horror story set in the underground network of abandoned railway tunnels in
Sydney, Australia, where a journalist and her crew discover something horrifying lurking within the tunnels.
The film explores themes of australia, investigation,
cover-up, water shortage, conspiracy.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.